DOAN HUU NOI

+65-8434-2003 \display doanhuunoi@gmail.com \display noidh.github.io

EDUCATION

Soongsil University, Seoul, South Korea Sept 2013 - July 2015 Master's Degree in Video & Image Processing. Post and Telecom. Institute of Tech., HCM City, Vietnam Sept 2008 - Jan 2013 Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology.

BACKGROUND

C++, Python, Pytorch, SIMD (SSE, AVX, NEON), TensorRT, OpenCV, Open3D, **Programming**

OpenGL, QT, MFC, CUDA, CMake

Research Image Processing, Computer Vision, Deep Learning, Stereo Vision, Depth Es-

timation, 3D Gaussian Splatting, Pattern Matching, Object Detection, Machine

Learning, 3D Rendering, Defect Inspection, Model Deployment

Language Vietnamese, Korean, English

EXPERIENCE

Nov. 2022 - Current Zoom Video Processing Software Engineer Singapore

· Participating in optimization tasks of the core image processing library.

- · Participating in 3D-telepresence project
 - Conducted the system setup: camera setup, intrinsic calibration, stereo calibration, multiple cameras synchronization.
 - Conducted the data collection: synthesis data and real data.
 - Supported the model development: Depth net (based on RAFT-Stereo), Render Net (based on 3DGS), optimizing using TensorRT.
 - Designed and implemented full pipeline of the demo program: Using Python, Pytorch and OpenGL Cubemap (to be ported into C++ version)
- Tech Stack: C++, Python, Pytorch, SIMD, TensorRT, Open3D, OpenCV, OpenGL, Video Processing, Deep Learning, 3D Rendering, 3D Gaussian Splatting, Depth Estimation, Model Deployment.

MVTech Nov. 2018 - Nov.2022 South Korea

Image Processing Researcher

- · Participated in developing a computer vision processing framework (named RAVID)
 - Developed the Shape Finder algorithm which is a feature-based matching algorithm. (View Demo)
 - Developing very fast convolution and morphology operations using SIMD and In-place Processing.
 - Developed a simple printed character recognition algorithm based on NCC.
- · Developed defect detection algorithms for semi-conductor inspection machines.
- · Tech Stack: C++, SIMD, Image Processing, Computer Vision.

Feb. 2017 - Oct. 2018 Enscape South Korea Software Engineer

- · Developed defect inspection algorithms using Halcon library.
- · Developed applications for semi-conductor inspection machines.
- · Tech Stack: C++, MFC, Halcon, OpenCV, SIMD.

Software Engineer

Sept 2015 - Oct. 2016 South Korea

- · Developed Android applications for a human skin analysis kit.
- Tech Stack: C++, Java, Android

PUBLICATION

Google Scholar Profile

- 1. A Method for matching pattern using image and an apparatus of thereof, HN. Doan, KS. Kwon,S. Korea Domestic Patent, 2021, No: 1024319840000, View Demo.
- 2. Method for hole filling in 3D model, and recording medium and apparatus for performing the same, US Patent, MC. Hong, BS. Kim, TD. Nguyen, HN. Doan, 2018, PDF.
- 3. Hole-Filling algorithm with spatio-temporal background information for view synthesis, IEICE Trans. on Information and Systems, HN. Doan, TD. Nguyen, MC. Hong, 2017, PDF.
- 4. A spatial-temporal hole filling approach with background modeling and texture synthesis for 3D video, Proceedings of the 2015 Conf. on research in adaptive and convergent systems, HN. Doan, MC. Hong, 2015, Link.
- 5. Hole filling algorithm using spatial-temporal background depth map for view synthesis in free view point television, Pacific Rim Conf. on Multimedia, HN. Doan, BS. Kim, MC. Hong, 2015, Link.
- 6. Directional hole filling algorithm in new view synthesis for 3D video using local segmentation, Proceedings of the 2014 Conf. on Research in Adaptive and Convergent Systems, HN. Doan, TA. Nguyen, MC. Hong, 2014, Link.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Technical Blog

I write articles to describe what I have learnt about Image Processing, Computer Vision, Machine Learning, 3D Rendering and other miscellaneous. Moreover, I develop the XImageTool application to demonstrate how those algorithms work intuitively.

XImageTool

XImage Tool is a free tool used for simulating fundamental Image Processing, Computer Vision, Machine Learning algorithms and 3D Rendering.

XText

XText is a free OCR software.